Music
As a big theme I'm imagining theme parts.
I want to have a big voice, and I want to have a big costume.
So, I found a costume that I really like in the show, and I made it look like that, and this is what I did.
A little bit of steam-pumping and bright knobs...
Eiiiit play!
You're going to get mad!
Eito play! Eito play! Eito play!
I'm not trying to be a play.
I just thought it would be nice if I could wear a hat or a bangle or something this time.
So...
How's that sound?
How's it going?
Yeah. - Yeah.
Eit-play!
That's right.
I really want to make the customer feel like they've come to Eito-Play! I want the customers to have the impression that they have come to
I like the impression of the parts.
Yes, yes, yes.
Is there anything else?
Um, no.
It's okay, because that's easy to understand.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
It's okay.
Yay! It's easy to understand!
Well, of course it is.
Eitai play!
Thank you for waiting!
It's all black!
Yamamachi.
What?
He's tall.
Why?
You don't know.
What? She's cute!
Oh, you're so cute!
That's amazing, genius! That's amazing, genius.
Genius.
If you take it a little too far, you might get a little weepy.
I'll try not to.
It's so good!
Oh, it's so cute!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I'm giggling.
I'm gonna goof off.
Oh, my gosh.
Hey.
LOL!
I'm going to take a visual.
Yes, sir.
What do you have in mind?
At first I thought Maihama would be nice.
But then I thought that if the costumes were colorful, it would be fine if they were simple.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do you think?
Yes, I do.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Yes. Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
It's got an encode.
That's great.
I'm not in costume.
I'm not putting in a costume.
If you hold it up vertically, you can see the lines.
Are you a genius?
He's cute.
It's cute.
Very nice.
Enterprise
So cute!
Very nice
It's good.
I might cry.
I like him so much, I want to be him.
I was going for “I want to be.
I like your tie.
That's great.
Thank you so much.
It's funny down there.
Oh, my goodness. I'm so happy!
That's great.
I still love Steedance!
I'm impressed.
Cute!
Cute
I'm not sure about the specifications of the tie on this one.
I can't put it on.
What do you think?
It's super cute.
It's really...
I thought I was...
I thought I was a cast member.
When I was editing this video
I'm not sure if I'm going to put in a “P” or not.
I'm not sure if I'm going to include it or not.
I'm not sure if I'm going to put P in it.
I'm about 90% P.
If I put in P, it's probably...
90% P.
If I put P in, it's probably...
That's great!
Miki is great!
Miki, you're amazing!
I don't have any.
Zero.
Seriously, it's real.
I'm so happy
Now that I can wear this by myself.
I told the makeup artist
I said to the makeup artist.
I said, “I want you to make me look good today. I said, “I want you to look good today.
I told the make-up artist
Man face
Really?
I want to be popular
By girls.
Yes, ma'am.
Uh...
Oh.
Jan
Ji kl
ощ
Ah, something like this will happen
Something like this
Oh my gosh
Even though I laughed
I'm so happy
Oh, my gosh!
That's so cute.
It's wrapped.
Thank you.
It's shocking.
Your hair looks short.
I'm a train pusher, aren't I?
Why are you such a toddler?
You must have felt like you were 5 years old.
Thank you very much.
I saw you when you were about five.
I put on the option car. I added an option car.
It's cute.
That really put you on the defensive a little bit.
There goes P again.
Is this the one I'm driving?
This is the one I'm driving.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hey, man.
Oh, man.
I'm so happy that you've been able to make something that's so perfect.
I'm so happy that you could make something that exceeds my ideals.
It's overwhelming!
There's nothing undersized!
I can't believe it!
I thought the dancer's costume was cute.
I thought that character's costume was really cute.
I didn't expect to have something like that made for me.
I'm so happy to have a chance to wear it
I'm so happy to have a chance to wear it.
You are all geniuses!
The pattern on the tie is actually really cute.
And they added a new one just now.
The color of the pants is pretty cute too!
I'm going to draw!
I draw pictures!
I also had a hat made.
I've never seen a costume with so many decorations.
It's quite fresh.
I'm so happy!
I'm really happy.
This year, when I think of Miki Yamauchi
I thought that Miki Yamauchi is a “XX”.
I was able to get her to wear such a beautiful costume.
I thought it would be great if I could bring out the darker side of my concept
I'm in the process of thinking about it and thinking about it a lot.
I'm thinking about it and thinking about it and thinking about it.
I'm sure there are people who have never been to Dreamland.
I'm sure there are some of you who have never been to Yumen-no-Kuni. If so, please join us!
Gang Parade and
We will take you to the dreamland of gang parade.
by all means, everyone!
Let's have a wonderful and happy day with us!
Let's have a wonderful and happy day together!
In my costume
My concept
Hmph.
Thank you for your time
Thank you for watching!